http://www.insideradio.com/site/help.html

Podcast News Daily
Having problems with the Inside Radio Email? Email Here.Need a refeed of today's issue of INSIDE RADIO? Call 800-248-4242 x 700 or Email Here.  Email Server Level WhitelistingIf you’re having difficulty receiving Inside Radio emails, it’s likely because your company's server is blocking our domain (insideradio.com or e2ma.net). There are many reasons why a Spam filter might do this — it could be due your IT/email administrator taking an aggressive stance against commercial messages, or a filter may have been programmed to not allow the same message to be sent to many different recipients at the same time.Keep in mind that we are media company delivering email to other media companies. As a media company, your company's spam parameters may be set to a high level to protect you from receiving a high percentage of spam. However, since Inside Radio is a news source and a media company as well, it is important that you relay to your IT dept that we are a trusted sender.Please consider sending whitelisting information (see below) to your company’s IT team so they can adjust their Spam filter to accept email delivery of Inside Radio.Email Safe Sender Inbox Whitelisting Even if a Spam filter is allowing your messages through, it may on occasion place them in the Spam folder for one or more recipients. To ensure that you continue receiving our messages in your Inbox, please add our “From” domain name (radionews@insideradio.com) to your safe senders list. How To: Desktop level whitelisting is quick and easy and only needs to be done one time, but every email program does it slightly differently. Email Delivery IP Information:We use a third party to deliver our emails, www.MyEmma.com strives for safe and secure email delivery.MyEmma WhiteList Information Here*Sending domain: e2ma.net ( from:radionews@insideradio.com )*IP Range:66.179.93.120/29 (66.179.93.120-127)*IP Range:66.179.147.160/27 (66.179.147.160-191)*IP Range:66.179.68.0/26 (66.179.68.0-63)*IP Range:66.179.102.0/25 (66.179.102.0-127)I've tried to login but my user name does not work? Are you a subscriber? If you are a paid subscriber, you are eligible for a login and password. Call 800-248-4242 x700 to set-up. (Only paid subscribers are eligible to login to the website.)  INSIDE RADIO Email Image download problemsIt is a known fact that Outlook 2007-10 running on Windows Vista/7 Home editions using the PC platform does not render rotating .gif files. If you are running this platform, please be aware that some images will not rotate. If you are not seeing images at all in your email, be sure to search your software for solutions. Block/Unblock Images in Outlook | Display images in Yahoo Mail | Display images in Gmail | View blocked images or automaticall download images in Windows Live Mail
Most Popular Stories
More Advertisers Are Using Live Reads. Technology Helps Scale Their Campaigns.
Analyst Predicts Global Podcast Revenue Will Top Over a Billion Dollars This Year.
Townsquare CEO Bill Wilson ‘Feeling Quite Good’ About Q4.
Supreme Court To Hear Media Ownership Case In January.
© Copyright 2020 Insideradio.com, PO Box 742263 Atlanta, GA | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
New Privacy and Terms of Use Policies
Our privacy policy and terms of use are changing to better explain the data we collect, how we use it, and to give you more information about your rights and choices with respect to your data. By continuing to use our services, you accept our new privacy policy and terms of use.
Privacy Policy
I Accept
We encourage you to review our privacy policy and terms of use.
